Those connectivity is unstable. Okay. We're back. We're recording again. I
don't see the recording It
said that it's recording. Like, it shows on my screen than it is. So Okay. Mine
does not say that.
I mean, heard the message saying it was recorded.
It's recording again. Go ahead before you lose it again.
Okay. Luck everybody. Be quick.
So I just wanted to say thank you to Jerry. What you said is what I have been trying to say. And I was wondering, I missed the beginning of the meeting. I apologize for that. Is it possible to put a question on referendum
or question to the town that like, would people support it increase by, I don't know, 1 mil or 0.5 mil specifically to fund a community center? I know that Adrian brought that up last night, and it seemed like that was a thing for the future, but is there a reason why we cannot do that now in an effort to bring the community together?
I do not have the answer for that. I don't think we can do it on a budget referendum. I think that's a separate item.
Or like another question to say, would people,
I don't, yeah. They don't even have the cost yet for the for the community center. We don't we have no idea what what No. But you're already saving money for it. So can't we save more money by taking it in taxes?
In
theory. Yeah. I mean What's the negative?